<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>poultry on Martin cooks</title>
    <link>https://cmbtea.github.io/martin-kocht/en/tags/poultry/</link>
    <description>Recent content in poultry on Martin cooks</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-en</language>
    <copyright>Martin kocht © {year}</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 26 Feb 2017 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://cmbtea.github.io/martin-kocht/en/tags/poultry/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Chicken Curry Monty Python</title>
      <link>https://cmbtea.github.io/martin-kocht/en/rezepte/chicken-curry-monty-python/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Feb 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cmbtea.github.io/martin-kocht/en/rezepte/chicken-curry-monty-python/</guid>
      <description>Profile This is a recipe from a book that has been modified slightly. The author is as me a fan of Monty Python. You may add a special taste by the Thai Sauce. Together with the oven vegetables and rice you have a perfect and delicious menu in less than an hour.
Ingredients  600g chicken breast 1 spoon flour 1/2 teaspoon ginger powder 1/2 teaspoon sweet paprika powder 1/2 teaspoon galangal powder (if you don’t have that use a bit more of the curry powder) 1 teaspoon cayenne pepper 1 spoon curry powder 2 onions a bit ginger 500ml vegetable soup (instant) 1 glas mango chutney Creme Fraiche Butter  Let&amp;rsquo;s go Cut the onions pretty fine and chop the ginger:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Coq au vin</title>
      <link>https://cmbtea.github.io/martin-kocht/en/rezepte/coq-au-vin/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cmbtea.github.io/martin-kocht/en/rezepte/coq-au-vin/</guid>
      <description>Profile This is a fairly elaborate recipe with some variations from a book. It takes time to prepare it, but it tastes so much better. All ingredients should be given separately. Later, everything cooks together.
Ingredients  spring onions Shallot, Champignons Casareccida noodles Bacon 1 chicken or one breast (with skin), 2 clubs, 4 wings 1 bottle of red wine (ideal is Burgundy but Cotes du Rhone is good as well, but not too cheap)) 1 pin of Cognac or Calvados Flour Butter oil Thyme, rosemary and parsley Salt, pepper  Let&amp;rsquo;s go The ingredients, part 1.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Corn salad with chicken liver in balsamico</title>
      <link>https://cmbtea.github.io/martin-kocht/en/rezepte/corn-salad/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cmbtea.github.io/martin-kocht/en/rezepte/corn-salad/</guid>
      <description>Profile This is one of my self invented recipes. Many people don’t like liver, but for those who like it it’s a nice alternative to the usual preparation.
You can use the same sauce (a glass of each balsamico, red wine and water) also for steaks. Refer to this recipe: Steaks with mushrooms in balsamico.
Ingredients  Chicken liver (or if you can’t get it, turkey liver), 200g per person 1-2 onions sliced in rings Garlic Flour Half a glass of balsamico 1 -1,5 teaspoon of sugar Olive oil Baguette  Let&amp;rsquo;s go Prepare the corn salad using your preferred dressing.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>