<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Martin cooks</title>
    <link>https://cmbtea.github.io/martin-kocht/en/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Martin cooks</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-en</language>
    <copyright>Martin kocht © {year}</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 20 Dec 2017 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://cmbtea.github.io/martin-kocht/en/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Shashlik (shish kebab)</title>
      <link>https://cmbtea.github.io/martin-kocht/en/rezepte/shashlik/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Dec 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cmbtea.github.io/martin-kocht/en/rezepte/shashlik/</guid>
      <description>Profile This is a completely unhealthy dish. Except onions there are no vegetables, just pure meat in a sauce. Typical man food that my mom made sometimes on Saturday evenings when I was a small boy. As I like it so much I started preparing this and modified it a bit. Here is my version of the Hungarian dish.
The original recipe uses different innards such as liver and kidney but I prefer it best with beef.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Salad with salmon</title>
      <link>https://cmbtea.github.io/martin-kocht/en/rezepte/salad-withssalmon/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Apr 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cmbtea.github.io/martin-kocht/en/rezepte/salad-withssalmon/</guid>
      <description>Profile Sometimes you do not have much time to cook, like me currently. Than it’s nice to prepare a quick dish that is deliciuous. This one takes about 15 minutes and is also simple.
Typically I add 4-5 olives but today I forgot to buy them. You can use any kind of fish, just one small piece is enough. I get the fish from Antonio and you can find him here:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Asparagus Asian style</title>
      <link>https://cmbtea.github.io/martin-kocht/en/rezepte/asparagus-asian-style/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Apr 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cmbtea.github.io/martin-kocht/en/rezepte/asparagus-asian-style/</guid>
      <description>Profile This is a good change to the traditional German style asparagus. In Germany, typically white asparagus is eaten, while elsewhere it is more likely to eat green asparagus. This asparagus is roasted and gives a splendid combination with the sharp chili and the sesame oil. If you don’t like green asparagus or can’t get white asparagus just use the color you like and can get.
You can get good asparagus from April to June on the weekly market in Gröbenzell (every Friday morning).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Leg of lamb</title>
      <link>https://cmbtea.github.io/martin-kocht/en/rezepte/leg-of-lamb/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Apr 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cmbtea.github.io/martin-kocht/en/rezepte/leg-of-lamb/</guid>
      <description>Profile In Germany lamb is a traditional Eastern dish. This lamb tastes excellent due to the low temperature, but preparing it takes very long. The club here (1.3Kg) took 3 hours. Larger need 3.5 hours, smaller 2.5. The sauce is optional. For this it needs bones and if you can get them it makes a lot of sense.
Ingredients  A leg of lamb of roughly 1,3Kg Thym Garlic 2 Spoons olive oil 1 Lemmon  For the sauce  1/2 bottle red wine Root vegetables 1 Piece (2cm) ginger 1 Spoon herb mixture ‘Herbes de Provence’ (Rosemary, Thyme and Savory) Nutmeg 1 Spoon instant beef or lamb broth 1 Spoon butter 1 Spoon flour  Let&amp;rsquo;s go The ingredients for the lamb:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Smoked pork &#39;Kasseler&#39;</title>
      <link>https://cmbtea.github.io/martin-kocht/en/rezepte/smoked-pork-kasseler/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Apr 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cmbtea.github.io/martin-kocht/en/rezepte/smoked-pork-kasseler/</guid>
      <description>Profile This recipe is the only one I know that doesn’t need any additional spices or herbs, not even salt. It’s always working if you follow the instructions, it’s simple and perfect for cold winter days. The only important thing is to get the right meat. At the ButcherSalzberger  you will get the right piece in the right quality. On Friday mornings you will find him on the market in Gröbenzell:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Asian squid</title>
      <link>https://cmbtea.github.io/martin-kocht/en/rezepte/asian-squid/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Apr 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cmbtea.github.io/martin-kocht/en/rezepte/asian-squid/</guid>
      <description>Profile I enjoyed this squid while traveling to Taiwan some weeks ago. That was on the night market in Kenting, in the very south of Taiwan:
embed google map.mapouter{position:relative;text-align:right;height:500px;width:600px;}.gmap_canvas {overflow:hidden;background:none!important;height:500px;width:600px;} They are fantastic and easy to be prepared. The sauce is a trial to redo it. Maybe someone correct it in the comments. In such case: thank you very much.
Of course the squid is from Antonio:
embed google map.mapouter{position:relative;text-align:right;height:500px;width:600px;}.gmap_canvas {overflow:hidden;background:none!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chicken Curry Monty Python</title>
      <link>https://cmbtea.github.io/martin-kocht/en/rezepte/chicken-curry-monty-python/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Feb 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cmbtea.github.io/martin-kocht/en/rezepte/chicken-curry-monty-python/</guid>
      <description>Profile This is a recipe from a book that has been modified slightly. The author is as me a fan of Monty Python. You may add a special taste by the Thai Sauce. Together with the oven vegetables and rice you have a perfect and delicious menu in less than an hour.
Ingredients  600g chicken breast 1 spoon flour 1/2 teaspoon ginger powder 1/2 teaspoon sweet paprika powder 1/2 teaspoon galangal powder (if you don’t have that use a bit more of the curry powder) 1 teaspoon cayenne pepper 1 spoon curry powder 2 onions a bit ginger 500ml vegetable soup (instant) 1 glas mango chutney Creme Fraiche Butter  Let&amp;rsquo;s go Cut the onions pretty fine and chop the ginger:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Oven Vegetables</title>
      <link>https://cmbtea.github.io/martin-kocht/en/rezepte/oven-vegetables/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Feb 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cmbtea.github.io/martin-kocht/en/rezepte/oven-vegetables/</guid>
      <description>Profile This is a pretty simple recipe for vegetables made in the oven. You can prepare it fast and within 30 minutes it’s ready. You can use different type of vegetables such as zucchini and aubergines. It’s a perfect add-on for a good Curry or you can use this Thai Sauce to add a special taste.
Ingredients  2 Paprika 1 Onion 2 rods of leek 2 rods of spring onions 500g Champignon 2 spoon olive oil herb mixture ‘Herbes de Provence’ (Rosemary, Thyme and Savory) Salt  Let&amp;rsquo;s go The ingredients:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Thai sauce</title>
      <link>https://cmbtea.github.io/martin-kocht/en/rezepte/thai-sauce/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Feb 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cmbtea.github.io/martin-kocht/en/rezepte/thai-sauce/</guid>
      <description>Profile This sauce is perfect for any kind of curry. Just add a bit on top of a curry, but caution: it’s hot. You can also enjoy it with oven-vegetables. It’s easy to prepare and you will always succeed preparing it.
Ingredients  Coriander Ginger 2-5 Chili, as much as you like 2-3 Garlic cloves 2 Spoons fish sauce 2 Spoons soy sauce 2 Spoons sweet and sour sauce  Let&amp;rsquo;s go The ingredients:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Moules Frites</title>
      <link>https://cmbtea.github.io/martin-kocht/en/rezepte/moules-frites/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Feb 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cmbtea.github.io/martin-kocht/en/rezepte/moules-frites/</guid>
      <description>Profile This is a great combo from the south of France. During the vacation we always enjoy it and even in Paris you will find a restaurant serving it. Of course you will not find the best in Paris, but in the Leon de Bruxelles (a Belgian Restaurant) the Moules Frites are great:
embed google map.mapouter{position:relative;text-align:right;height:500px;width:600px;}.gmap_canvas {overflow:hidden;background:none!important;height:500px;width:600px;} In the old part of Nice at the Mediterranean sea you will them in lots of places in a fantastic quality.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The best Spaghetti Bolognese</title>
      <link>https://cmbtea.github.io/martin-kocht/en/rezepte/spaghetti-bolognese/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Feb 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cmbtea.github.io/martin-kocht/en/rezepte/spaghetti-bolognese/</guid>
      <description>Profile We all know the things we liked at home as kids and that we still love today. These Spaghetti are such a recipe that I still cook frequently and that we all love a lot. If it is too much you can keep the sauce for the next day and warm it up without loosing the great taste. You may also keep it in the freezer for some time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Marinated fried herring</title>
      <link>https://cmbtea.github.io/martin-kocht/en/rezepte/marinated-fried-herring/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cmbtea.github.io/martin-kocht/en/rezepte/marinated-fried-herring/</guid>
      <description>Profile When making fried herring, there are two things to consider: You only make kippers once in the house and never again afterwards because it smells bad and lasts a long time. Secondly, it makes no sense to make only a few herrings. Do it rather directly on the terrace or balcony and take at least a dozen herring.
Ingredients  20 Herrings 6-8 Onions salt-pepper mixture (you need a lot) Flour 4-5 bay leaves Mustard seeds 10 juniper berries 1,5l vinegar (not too bad) 1,5l water  Let&amp;rsquo;s go Wash and drain the herrings.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Coq au vin</title>
      <link>https://cmbtea.github.io/martin-kocht/en/rezepte/coq-au-vin/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cmbtea.github.io/martin-kocht/en/rezepte/coq-au-vin/</guid>
      <description>Profile This is a fairly elaborate recipe with some variations from a book. It takes time to prepare it, but it tastes so much better. All ingredients should be given separately. Later, everything cooks together.
Ingredients  spring onions Shallot, Champignons Casareccida noodles Bacon 1 chicken or one breast (with skin), 2 clubs, 4 wings 1 bottle of red wine (ideal is Burgundy but Cotes du Rhone is good as well, but not too cheap)) 1 pin of Cognac or Calvados Flour Butter oil Thyme, rosemary and parsley Salt, pepper  Let&amp;rsquo;s go The ingredients, part 1.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Basic mix for a tartar</title>
      <link>https://cmbtea.github.io/martin-kocht/en/rezepte/tartar-basic-mix/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cmbtea.github.io/martin-kocht/en/rezepte/tartar-basic-mix/</guid>
      <description>Profile This is my basic mix for a tartar. You can vary it quite a bit. For example, a few drops of sesame oil and sesame seeds. Sprinkle chilli, parsley, etc. No matter how you change it, the basic recipe is a good basis.
Ingredients  500g tatar (a good steak, not too fat is perfect) 2 eggs 1 onion 4 anchovy fillets Capers 1 tablespoon soy sauce 1 tablespoon sweet-sour sauce 2 tsp ketchup Breadcrumbs  Let&amp;rsquo;s go Even if only 1 egg is to be seen here, you need 2 eggs for 500g tartar.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Roast saddle of venison</title>
      <link>https://cmbtea.github.io/martin-kocht/en/rezepte/roast-saddle-of-venison/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cmbtea.github.io/martin-kocht/en/rezepte/roast-saddle-of-venison/</guid>
      <description>Profile This is a typical German Christmas dinner. A bit elaborate and therefore you should plan enough time. The venison is made at low temperature. You should check your cooker if it can keep the temperature constant and what the setting is for exactly 80°. A too high or low temperature would be fatal.
Ingredients For the roast  1 saddle of venison and, if that is not enough, an upper leg A sprig of rosemary and thyme  For the roast stock  All that remains of the deer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Roulade</title>
      <link>https://cmbtea.github.io/martin-kocht/en/rezepte/roulade/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cmbtea.github.io/martin-kocht/en/rezepte/roulade/</guid>
      <description>Profile Like some dishes, roulades are best prepared the day before and warmed up the next day. It is also important that you have kitchen yarn to wrap the roulades, brackets do not hold this variant together. This is a slightly variated version of the traditional German roulade. If you prefer the original one just remove the paprika and the leek.
Ingredients  Roulades 1 slice of bacon per roulade 1 garden leek 1 paprika Pickled gherkins hot and mild mustard 2 onions Tomato paste Beef broth  Let&amp;rsquo;s go We need of course the roulade and best of all some more for the next day.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Saffron Spaghetti</title>
      <link>https://cmbtea.github.io/martin-kocht/en/rezepte/saffron-spaghetti/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cmbtea.github.io/martin-kocht/en/rezepte/saffron-spaghetti/</guid>
      <description>Profile Tills favorite spaghetti. Re-cooked from the Poseidon at the Viktualienmarkt in Munich.
The Poseidon is actually a fishmonger which offers some places for lunch. However it’s pretty crowded and especially during the summer it’s difficult to get one of the rare seats outside. But it is worth to wait, for example for a fantastic fish soup. The Poseidon can be found here:
embed google map.mapouter{position:relative;text-align:right;height:500px;width:600px;}.gmap_canvas {overflow:hidden;background:none!important;height:500px;width:600px;} Ingredients  2 calamari 1 handful Vongole (other mussels are also fine) Shrimps for Till or better 4 Black Tiger shrimp 8 small tomatoes 1 glass of fish soup 1 cup of cream 1 small glass of white wine Tomato paste 1 onion Garlic 1 teaspoon sugar 0.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stuffed pork fillet with gnocchi and cauliflower</title>
      <link>https://cmbtea.github.io/martin-kocht/en/rezepte/stuffed-pork-fillet/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cmbtea.github.io/martin-kocht/en/rezepte/stuffed-pork-fillet/</guid>
      <description>Profile This is a fairly elaborate recipe from a book, but you’re rewarded for the effort, it’s fantastic. Of course you can also save a filling, but the first time you could try both of them. Like other dishes before it is made at low temperature. At this point, the categories should be pointed out. So you can quickly find all low temperature recipes.
Ingredients For the first filling  1 pepper Thyme A handful walnuts  For the second filling  Dried tomatoes in oil 1-2 branches of rosemary A handful pine nuts  For frying and for the sauce  1 teaspoon sugar 30g Butter 500ml passed tomatoes 100ml vegetable broth  Let&amp;rsquo;s go The ingredients for the first filling.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Corn salad with chicken liver in balsamico</title>
      <link>https://cmbtea.github.io/martin-kocht/en/rezepte/corn-salad/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cmbtea.github.io/martin-kocht/en/rezepte/corn-salad/</guid>
      <description>Profile This is one of my self invented recipes. Many people don’t like liver, but for those who like it it’s a nice alternative to the usual preparation.
You can use the same sauce (a glass of each balsamico, red wine and water) also for steaks. Refer to this recipe: Steaks with mushrooms in balsamico.
Ingredients  Chicken liver (or if you can’t get it, turkey liver), 200g per person 1-2 onions sliced in rings Garlic Flour Half a glass of balsamico 1 -1,5 teaspoon of sugar Olive oil Baguette  Let&amp;rsquo;s go Prepare the corn salad using your preferred dressing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fish pan with salad or spaghetti</title>
      <link>https://cmbtea.github.io/martin-kocht/en/rezepte/fish-pan/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cmbtea.github.io/martin-kocht/en/rezepte/fish-pan/</guid>
      <description>Profile This delicious meal is prepared within minutes and can be enjoyed with spaghetti or with a salad.
Ingredients  Approx. 1Kg fish fillet cut into small pieces (what is currently on offer) Olives Garlic 2 chilies 1 glass of wine (recipe for 2x spaghetti plus 2x salad each) 1/2 lemon salt, pepper Spices (see text) Salad with favorite dressing  Let&amp;rsquo;s go Marinate fish and leek (in fine strips) in olive oil</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Linguine with salmon and spinach</title>
      <link>https://cmbtea.github.io/martin-kocht/en/rezepte/linguine-with-salmon-and-spinace/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cmbtea.github.io/martin-kocht/en/rezepte/linguine-with-salmon-and-spinace/</guid>
      <description>Profile The spinach is the most important in this recipe. It took some iterations to find out that spinach is the thing to be added to provide the special taste in combination with the salmon. Give it a try if you like salmon pasta, you will not be disappointed.
Ingredients  1 onion Garlic 5-6 cherry tomatoes Spring onions Spinach according to your wishes. Some handful is typically enough Salmon fillet (200-250g per person) 1 teaspoon sugar 1 teaspoon vegetable broth 1 can Creme Fine or Creme Fraiche Olive oil Fish sauce or oyster sauce (Asia market).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sashimi</title>
      <link>https://cmbtea.github.io/martin-kocht/en/rezepte/sashimi/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cmbtea.github.io/martin-kocht/en/rezepte/sashimi/</guid>
      <description>Profile Simple food with only the fish as an imporant ingredient. It should come from the fishmonger of your trust. You can prepare this dish in minutes and it’s perfect as a starter.
I get my fish from Antonio having a seperate business in the Tutti Gusto in Gröbenzell. He always sells different fish in Sushi quality. You will find the Tutti Gusto here:
embed google map.mapouter{position:relative;text-align:right;height:500px;width:600px;}.gmap_canvas {overflow:hidden;background:none!important;height:500px;width:600px;} My source for the Soba sauce is the Asia food shop in Olching.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Steaks with mushrooms in balsamico with gnocchi</title>
      <link>https://cmbtea.github.io/martin-kocht/en/rezepte/steaks-with-mushrooms/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cmbtea.github.io/martin-kocht/en/rezepte/steaks-with-mushrooms/</guid>
      <description>Profile The quality of the steaks are the most important ingredient in this recipe. It’s best to cut them freshly from a whole Roastbeef and to cook them not too cold but at room temperature. The sauce can be used for other dishes such as the chicken liver salad given here Salad with chicken liver.
You can use the same sauce for a nice salad such as this one: Corn salad with chicken liver in balsamico.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>