<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>_german on Martin cooks</title>
    <link>https://cmbtea.github.io/martin-kocht/en/tags/_german/</link>
    <description>Recent content in _german on Martin cooks</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-en</language>
    <copyright>Martin kocht © {year}</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 16 Apr 2017 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://cmbtea.github.io/martin-kocht/en/tags/_german/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Leg of lamb</title>
      <link>https://cmbtea.github.io/martin-kocht/en/rezepte/leg-of-lamb/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Apr 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cmbtea.github.io/martin-kocht/en/rezepte/leg-of-lamb/</guid>
      <description>Profile In Germany lamb is a traditional Eastern dish. This lamb tastes excellent due to the low temperature, but preparing it takes very long. The club here (1.3Kg) took 3 hours. Larger need 3.5 hours, smaller 2.5. The sauce is optional. For this it needs bones and if you can get them it makes a lot of sense.
Ingredients  A leg of lamb of roughly 1,3Kg Thym Garlic 2 Spoons olive oil 1 Lemmon  For the sauce  1/2 bottle red wine Root vegetables 1 Piece (2cm) ginger 1 Spoon herb mixture ‘Herbes de Provence’ (Rosemary, Thyme and Savory) Nutmeg 1 Spoon instant beef or lamb broth 1 Spoon butter 1 Spoon flour  Let&amp;rsquo;s go The ingredients for the lamb:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Smoked pork &#39;Kasseler&#39;</title>
      <link>https://cmbtea.github.io/martin-kocht/en/rezepte/smoked-pork-kasseler/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Apr 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cmbtea.github.io/martin-kocht/en/rezepte/smoked-pork-kasseler/</guid>
      <description>Profile This recipe is the only one I know that doesn’t need any additional spices or herbs, not even salt. It’s always working if you follow the instructions, it’s simple and perfect for cold winter days. The only important thing is to get the right meat. At the ButcherSalzberger  you will get the right piece in the right quality. On Friday mornings you will find him on the market in Gröbenzell:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Marinated fried herring</title>
      <link>https://cmbtea.github.io/martin-kocht/en/rezepte/marinated-fried-herring/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cmbtea.github.io/martin-kocht/en/rezepte/marinated-fried-herring/</guid>
      <description>Profile When making fried herring, there are two things to consider: You only make kippers once in the house and never again afterwards because it smells bad and lasts a long time. Secondly, it makes no sense to make only a few herrings. Do it rather directly on the terrace or balcony and take at least a dozen herring.
Ingredients  20 Herrings 6-8 Onions salt-pepper mixture (you need a lot) Flour 4-5 bay leaves Mustard seeds 10 juniper berries 1,5l vinegar (not too bad) 1,5l water  Let&amp;rsquo;s go Wash and drain the herrings.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Roast saddle of venison</title>
      <link>https://cmbtea.github.io/martin-kocht/en/rezepte/roast-saddle-of-venison/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cmbtea.github.io/martin-kocht/en/rezepte/roast-saddle-of-venison/</guid>
      <description>Profile This is a typical German Christmas dinner. A bit elaborate and therefore you should plan enough time. The venison is made at low temperature. You should check your cooker if it can keep the temperature constant and what the setting is for exactly 80°. A too high or low temperature would be fatal.
Ingredients For the roast  1 saddle of venison and, if that is not enough, an upper leg A sprig of rosemary and thyme  For the roast stock  All that remains of the deer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Roulade</title>
      <link>https://cmbtea.github.io/martin-kocht/en/rezepte/roulade/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cmbtea.github.io/martin-kocht/en/rezepte/roulade/</guid>
      <description>Profile Like some dishes, roulades are best prepared the day before and warmed up the next day. It is also important that you have kitchen yarn to wrap the roulades, brackets do not hold this variant together. This is a slightly variated version of the traditional German roulade. If you prefer the original one just remove the paprika and the leek.
Ingredients  Roulades 1 slice of bacon per roulade 1 garden leek 1 paprika Pickled gherkins hot and mild mustard 2 onions Tomato paste Beef broth  Let&amp;rsquo;s go We need of course the roulade and best of all some more for the next day.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stuffed pork fillet with gnocchi and cauliflower</title>
      <link>https://cmbtea.github.io/martin-kocht/en/rezepte/stuffed-pork-fillet/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cmbtea.github.io/martin-kocht/en/rezepte/stuffed-pork-fillet/</guid>
      <description>Profile This is a fairly elaborate recipe from a book, but you’re rewarded for the effort, it’s fantastic. Of course you can also save a filling, but the first time you could try both of them. Like other dishes before it is made at low temperature. At this point, the categories should be pointed out. So you can quickly find all low temperature recipes.
Ingredients For the first filling  1 pepper Thyme A handful walnuts  For the second filling  Dried tomatoes in oil 1-2 branches of rosemary A handful pine nuts  For frying and for the sauce  1 teaspoon sugar 30g Butter 500ml passed tomatoes 100ml vegetable broth  Let&amp;rsquo;s go The ingredients for the first filling.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>