<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>_french on Martin cooks</title>
    <link>https://cmbtea.github.io/martin-kocht/en/tags/_french/</link>
    <description>Recent content in _french on Martin cooks</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-en</language>
    <copyright>Martin kocht © {year}</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 19 Feb 2017 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://cmbtea.github.io/martin-kocht/en/tags/_french/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Moules Frites</title>
      <link>https://cmbtea.github.io/martin-kocht/en/rezepte/moules-frites/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Feb 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cmbtea.github.io/martin-kocht/en/rezepte/moules-frites/</guid>
      <description>Profile This is a great combo from the south of France. During the vacation we always enjoy it and even in Paris you will find a restaurant serving it. Of course you will not find the best in Paris, but in the Leon de Bruxelles (a Belgian Restaurant) the Moules Frites are great:
embed google map.mapouter{position:relative;text-align:right;height:500px;width:600px;}.gmap_canvas {overflow:hidden;background:none!important;height:500px;width:600px;} In the old part of Nice at the Mediterranean sea you will them in lots of places in a fantastic quality.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Coq au vin</title>
      <link>https://cmbtea.github.io/martin-kocht/en/rezepte/coq-au-vin/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cmbtea.github.io/martin-kocht/en/rezepte/coq-au-vin/</guid>
      <description>Profile This is a fairly elaborate recipe with some variations from a book. It takes time to prepare it, but it tastes so much better. All ingredients should be given separately. Later, everything cooks together.
Ingredients  spring onions Shallot, Champignons Casareccida noodles Bacon 1 chicken or one breast (with skin), 2 clubs, 4 wings 1 bottle of red wine (ideal is Burgundy but Cotes du Rhone is good as well, but not too cheap)) 1 pin of Cognac or Calvados Flour Butter oil Thyme, rosemary and parsley Salt, pepper  Let&amp;rsquo;s go The ingredients, part 1.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Basic mix for a tartar</title>
      <link>https://cmbtea.github.io/martin-kocht/en/rezepte/tartar-basic-mix/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cmbtea.github.io/martin-kocht/en/rezepte/tartar-basic-mix/</guid>
      <description>Profile This is my basic mix for a tartar. You can vary it quite a bit. For example, a few drops of sesame oil and sesame seeds. Sprinkle chilli, parsley, etc. No matter how you change it, the basic recipe is a good basis.
Ingredients  500g tatar (a good steak, not too fat is perfect) 2 eggs 1 onion 4 anchovy fillets Capers 1 tablespoon soy sauce 1 tablespoon sweet-sour sauce 2 tsp ketchup Breadcrumbs  Let&amp;rsquo;s go Even if only 1 egg is to be seen here, you need 2 eggs for 500g tartar.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>