<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>low-temperature on Martin cooks</title>
    <link>http://192.168.2.92/en/tags/low-temperature/</link>
    <description>Recent content in low-temperature on Martin cooks</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-en</language>
    <copyright>Martin kocht © {year}</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 16 Apr 2017 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://192.168.2.92/en/tags/low-temperature/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Leg of lamb</title>
      <link>http://192.168.2.92/en/rezepte/leg-of-lamb/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Apr 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://192.168.2.92/en/rezepte/leg-of-lamb/</guid>
      <description>Profile In Germany lamb is a traditional Eastern dish. This lamb tastes excellent due to the low temperature, but preparing it takes very long. The club here (1.3Kg) took 3 hours. Larger need 3.5 hours, smaller 2.5. The sauce is optional. For this it needs bones and if you can get them it makes a lot of sense.
Ingredients  A leg of lamb of roughly 1,3Kg Thym Garlic 2 Spoons olive oil 1 Lemmon  For the sauce  1/2 bottle red wine Root vegetables 1 Piece (2cm) ginger 1 Spoon herb mixture ‘Herbes de Provence’ (Rosemary, Thyme and Savory) Nutmeg 1 Spoon instant beef or lamb broth 1 Spoon butter 1 Spoon flour  Let&amp;rsquo;s go The ingredients for the lamb:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Roast saddle of venison</title>
      <link>http://192.168.2.92/en/rezepte/roast-saddle-of-venison/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://192.168.2.92/en/rezepte/roast-saddle-of-venison/</guid>
      <description>Profile This is a typical German Christmas dinner. A bit elaborate and therefore you should plan enough time. The venison is made at low temperature. You should check your cooker if it can keep the temperature constant and what the setting is for exactly 80°. A too high or low temperature would be fatal.
Ingredients For the roast  1 saddle of venison and, if that is not enough, an upper leg A sprig of rosemary and thyme  For the roast stock  All that remains of the deer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stuffed pork fillet with gnocchi and cauliflower</title>
      <link>http://192.168.2.92/en/rezepte/stuffed-pork-fillet/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://192.168.2.92/en/rezepte/stuffed-pork-fillet/</guid>
      <description>Profile This is a fairly elaborate recipe from a book, but you’re rewarded for the effort, it’s fantastic. Of course you can also save a filling, but the first time you could try both of them. Like other dishes before it is made at low temperature. At this point, the categories should be pointed out. So you can quickly find all low temperature recipes.
Ingredients For the first filling  1 pepper Thyme A handful walnuts  For the second filling  Dried tomatoes in oil 1-2 branches of rosemary A handful pine nuts  For frying and for the sauce  1 teaspoon sugar 30g Butter 500ml passed tomatoes 100ml vegetable broth  Let&amp;rsquo;s go The ingredients for the first filling.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>