<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>fish on Martin cooks</title>
    <link>https://cmbtea.github.io/martin-kocht/en/tags/fish/</link>
    <description>Recent content in fish on Martin cooks</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-en</language>
    <copyright>Martin kocht © {year}</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 30 Apr 2017 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://cmbtea.github.io/martin-kocht/en/tags/fish/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Salad with salmon</title>
      <link>https://cmbtea.github.io/martin-kocht/en/rezepte/salad-withssalmon/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Apr 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cmbtea.github.io/martin-kocht/en/rezepte/salad-withssalmon/</guid>
      <description>Profile Sometimes you do not have much time to cook, like me currently. Than it’s nice to prepare a quick dish that is deliciuous. This one takes about 15 minutes and is also simple.
Typically I add 4-5 olives but today I forgot to buy them. You can use any kind of fish, just one small piece is enough. I get the fish from Antonio and you can find him here:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Asian squid</title>
      <link>https://cmbtea.github.io/martin-kocht/en/rezepte/asian-squid/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Apr 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cmbtea.github.io/martin-kocht/en/rezepte/asian-squid/</guid>
      <description>Profile I enjoyed this squid while traveling to Taiwan some weeks ago. That was on the night market in Kenting, in the very south of Taiwan:
embed google map.mapouter{position:relative;text-align:right;height:500px;width:600px;}.gmap_canvas {overflow:hidden;background:none!important;height:500px;width:600px;} They are fantastic and easy to be prepared. The sauce is a trial to redo it. Maybe someone correct it in the comments. In such case: thank you very much.
Of course the squid is from Antonio:
embed google map.mapouter{position:relative;text-align:right;height:500px;width:600px;}.gmap_canvas {overflow:hidden;background:none!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Moules Frites</title>
      <link>https://cmbtea.github.io/martin-kocht/en/rezepte/moules-frites/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Feb 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cmbtea.github.io/martin-kocht/en/rezepte/moules-frites/</guid>
      <description>Profile This is a great combo from the south of France. During the vacation we always enjoy it and even in Paris you will find a restaurant serving it. Of course you will not find the best in Paris, but in the Leon de Bruxelles (a Belgian Restaurant) the Moules Frites are great:
embed google map.mapouter{position:relative;text-align:right;height:500px;width:600px;}.gmap_canvas {overflow:hidden;background:none!important;height:500px;width:600px;} In the old part of Nice at the Mediterranean sea you will them in lots of places in a fantastic quality.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Marinated fried herring</title>
      <link>https://cmbtea.github.io/martin-kocht/en/rezepte/marinated-fried-herring/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cmbtea.github.io/martin-kocht/en/rezepte/marinated-fried-herring/</guid>
      <description>Profile When making fried herring, there are two things to consider: You only make kippers once in the house and never again afterwards because it smells bad and lasts a long time. Secondly, it makes no sense to make only a few herrings. Do it rather directly on the terrace or balcony and take at least a dozen herring.
Ingredients  20 Herrings 6-8 Onions salt-pepper mixture (you need a lot) Flour 4-5 bay leaves Mustard seeds 10 juniper berries 1,5l vinegar (not too bad) 1,5l water  Let&amp;rsquo;s go Wash and drain the herrings.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Saffron Spaghetti</title>
      <link>https://cmbtea.github.io/martin-kocht/en/rezepte/saffron-spaghetti/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cmbtea.github.io/martin-kocht/en/rezepte/saffron-spaghetti/</guid>
      <description>Profile Tills favorite spaghetti. Re-cooked from the Poseidon at the Viktualienmarkt in Munich.
The Poseidon is actually a fishmonger which offers some places for lunch. However it’s pretty crowded and especially during the summer it’s difficult to get one of the rare seats outside. But it is worth to wait, for example for a fantastic fish soup. The Poseidon can be found here:
embed google map.mapouter{position:relative;text-align:right;height:500px;width:600px;}.gmap_canvas {overflow:hidden;background:none!important;height:500px;width:600px;} Ingredients  2 calamari 1 handful Vongole (other mussels are also fine) Shrimps for Till or better 4 Black Tiger shrimp 8 small tomatoes 1 glass of fish soup 1 cup of cream 1 small glass of white wine Tomato paste 1 onion Garlic 1 teaspoon sugar 0.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fish pan with salad or spaghetti</title>
      <link>https://cmbtea.github.io/martin-kocht/en/rezepte/fish-pan/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cmbtea.github.io/martin-kocht/en/rezepte/fish-pan/</guid>
      <description>Profile This delicious meal is prepared within minutes and can be enjoyed with spaghetti or with a salad.
Ingredients  Approx. 1Kg fish fillet cut into small pieces (what is currently on offer) Olives Garlic 2 chilies 1 glass of wine (recipe for 2x spaghetti plus 2x salad each) 1/2 lemon salt, pepper Spices (see text) Salad with favorite dressing  Let&amp;rsquo;s go Marinate fish and leek (in fine strips) in olive oil</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Linguine with salmon and spinach</title>
      <link>https://cmbtea.github.io/martin-kocht/en/rezepte/linguine-with-salmon-and-spinace/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cmbtea.github.io/martin-kocht/en/rezepte/linguine-with-salmon-and-spinace/</guid>
      <description>Profile The spinach is the most important in this recipe. It took some iterations to find out that spinach is the thing to be added to provide the special taste in combination with the salmon. Give it a try if you like salmon pasta, you will not be disappointed.
Ingredients  1 onion Garlic 5-6 cherry tomatoes Spring onions Spinach according to your wishes. Some handful is typically enough Salmon fillet (200-250g per person) 1 teaspoon sugar 1 teaspoon vegetable broth 1 can Creme Fine or Creme Fraiche Olive oil Fish sauce or oyster sauce (Asia market).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sashimi</title>
      <link>https://cmbtea.github.io/martin-kocht/en/rezepte/sashimi/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cmbtea.github.io/martin-kocht/en/rezepte/sashimi/</guid>
      <description>Profile Simple food with only the fish as an imporant ingredient. It should come from the fishmonger of your trust. You can prepare this dish in minutes and it’s perfect as a starter.
I get my fish from Antonio having a seperate business in the Tutti Gusto in Gröbenzell. He always sells different fish in Sushi quality. You will find the Tutti Gusto here:
embed google map.mapouter{position:relative;text-align:right;height:500px;width:600px;}.gmap_canvas {overflow:hidden;background:none!important;height:500px;width:600px;} My source for the Soba sauce is the Asia food shop in Olching.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>