<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>salad on Martin cooks</title>
    <link>https://cmbtea.github.io/martin-kocht/en/tags/salad/</link>
    <description>Recent content in salad on Martin cooks</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-en</language>
    <copyright>Martin kocht © {year}</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 30 Apr 2017 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://cmbtea.github.io/martin-kocht/en/tags/salad/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Salad with salmon</title>
      <link>https://cmbtea.github.io/martin-kocht/en/rezepte/salad-withssalmon/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Apr 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cmbtea.github.io/martin-kocht/en/rezepte/salad-withssalmon/</guid>
      <description>Profile Sometimes you do not have much time to cook, like me currently. Than it’s nice to prepare a quick dish that is deliciuous. This one takes about 15 minutes and is also simple.
Typically I add 4-5 olives but today I forgot to buy them. You can use any kind of fish, just one small piece is enough. I get the fish from Antonio and you can find him here:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Asian squid</title>
      <link>https://cmbtea.github.io/martin-kocht/en/rezepte/asian-squid/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Apr 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cmbtea.github.io/martin-kocht/en/rezepte/asian-squid/</guid>
      <description>Profile I enjoyed this squid while traveling to Taiwan some weeks ago. That was on the night market in Kenting, in the very south of Taiwan:
embed google map.mapouter{position:relative;text-align:right;height:500px;width:600px;}.gmap_canvas {overflow:hidden;background:none!important;height:500px;width:600px;} They are fantastic and easy to be prepared. The sauce is a trial to redo it. Maybe someone correct it in the comments. In such case: thank you very much.
Of course the squid is from Antonio:
embed google map.mapouter{position:relative;text-align:right;height:500px;width:600px;}.gmap_canvas {overflow:hidden;background:none!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Corn salad with chicken liver in balsamico</title>
      <link>https://cmbtea.github.io/martin-kocht/en/rezepte/corn-salad/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cmbtea.github.io/martin-kocht/en/rezepte/corn-salad/</guid>
      <description>Profile This is one of my self invented recipes. Many people don’t like liver, but for those who like it it’s a nice alternative to the usual preparation.
You can use the same sauce (a glass of each balsamico, red wine and water) also for steaks. Refer to this recipe: Steaks with mushrooms in balsamico.
Ingredients  Chicken liver (or if you can’t get it, turkey liver), 200g per person 1-2 onions sliced in rings Garlic Flour Half a glass of balsamico 1 -1,5 teaspoon of sugar Olive oil Baguette  Let&amp;rsquo;s go Prepare the corn salad using your preferred dressing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fish pan with salad or spaghetti</title>
      <link>https://cmbtea.github.io/martin-kocht/en/rezepte/fish-pan/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cmbtea.github.io/martin-kocht/en/rezepte/fish-pan/</guid>
      <description>Profile This delicious meal is prepared within minutes and can be enjoyed with spaghetti or with a salad.
Ingredients  Approx. 1Kg fish fillet cut into small pieces (what is currently on offer) Olives Garlic 2 chilies 1 glass of wine (recipe for 2x spaghetti plus 2x salad each) 1/2 lemon salt, pepper Spices (see text) Salad with favorite dressing  Let&amp;rsquo;s go Marinate fish and leek (in fine strips) in olive oil</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>