<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>pork on Martin cooks</title>
    <link>https://cmbtea.github.io/martin-kocht/en/tags/pork/</link>
    <description>Recent content in pork on Martin cooks</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-en</language>
    <copyright>Martin kocht © {year}</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 14 Apr 2017 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://cmbtea.github.io/martin-kocht/en/tags/pork/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Smoked pork &#39;Kasseler&#39;</title>
      <link>https://cmbtea.github.io/martin-kocht/en/rezepte/smoked-pork-kasseler/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Apr 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cmbtea.github.io/martin-kocht/en/rezepte/smoked-pork-kasseler/</guid>
      <description>Profile This recipe is the only one I know that doesn’t need any additional spices or herbs, not even salt. It’s always working if you follow the instructions, it’s simple and perfect for cold winter days. The only important thing is to get the right meat. At the ButcherSalzberger  you will get the right piece in the right quality. On Friday mornings you will find him on the market in Gröbenzell:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stuffed pork fillet with gnocchi and cauliflower</title>
      <link>https://cmbtea.github.io/martin-kocht/en/rezepte/stuffed-pork-fillet/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cmbtea.github.io/martin-kocht/en/rezepte/stuffed-pork-fillet/</guid>
      <description>Profile This is a fairly elaborate recipe from a book, but you’re rewarded for the effort, it’s fantastic. Of course you can also save a filling, but the first time you could try both of them. Like other dishes before it is made at low temperature. At this point, the categories should be pointed out. So you can quickly find all low temperature recipes.
Ingredients For the first filling  1 pepper Thyme A handful walnuts  For the second filling  Dried tomatoes in oil 1-2 branches of rosemary A handful pine nuts  For frying and for the sauce  1 teaspoon sugar 30g Butter 500ml passed tomatoes 100ml vegetable broth  Let&amp;rsquo;s go The ingredients for the first filling.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>